- Yeah, I'm gonna go pack a bag.
- No, you're not. You're gonna:
(Leonard:)Do we really have to wear
this camouflage crap to play paintball?
(Sheldon:)Who said that? Leonard,
I can hear your voice, but I can't see you.
(Leonard:)I'm not in the mood, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Oh, there you are.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I know you're upset
about recent events...
(Sheldon:)...and I have someone here to help.
I don't wanna talk to Amy.
Yeah... No, it's not Amy.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Hello, dear.
(Leonard:)You called my mother?
(Sheldon:)Oh, Leonard, is it really necessary
to caption the obvious?
(Dr Hofstadter:)He's been like that
since he was a toddler.
"Look, Mommy, a butterfly."
(Dr Hofstadter:)Maddening.
(Leonard:)What's going on?
What do you want?
(Dr Hofstadter:)Sheldon informed me that you're
experiencing an emotional upheaval...